export const dataBase = [
  {
    "Answer": "Xavier",
    "Question": " _____ Institute is the home of the X-Men",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "41",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ghost",
    "Question": "____ Rider, Marvel's motorcyle-riding superhero",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "47",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Ghost Rider",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Foggy",
    "Question": "_____ Nelson, the Daredevil's law partner",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "41",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Daredevil",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Pepper",
    "Question": "_____ Potts is Tony Stark's romantic interest",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "45",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Iron-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Infinity",
    "Question": "_____ Stones allow whoever wields them to have god-like powers",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "62",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Silver",
    "Question": "_____ Surfer, servant of Galactus who bretrayed him to save Earth",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "65",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Silver Surfer",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Scarlet",
    "Question": "_____ Witch, twin sister of Quicksilver",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "39",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Drax",
    "Question": "_____, the Destroyer",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "20",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Black",
    "Question": "______ Cat, ",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "12",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Amazing Spider-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Jessica",
    "Question": "______ Jones, a superhero turned private investigator",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "53",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Jessica Jones",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Winter",
    "Question": "_______ Soldier",
    "Answer Letters": "14",
    "Question Letters": "15",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Invisible",
    "Question": "_______ Woman, one of the Fantastic Four",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "40",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Fantastic Four",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Professor",
    "Question": "_______ X is the leader of the X-Men",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "36",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Daredevil",
    "Question": "A blind superhero who is a lawyer by day",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "40",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Daredevil",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hercules",
    "Question": "A character based on Greek mythology and a member of the Avengers",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "65",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Talos",
    "Question": "A cunning spy of the Skrull Empire, a master shapeshifter",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "57",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain Marvel",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hawkeye",
    "Question": "a deaf super hero",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "17",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Nightcrawler",
    "Question": "A devout Catholic with a demonic appearance",
    "Answer Letters": "12",
    "Question Letters": "43",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Lockjaw",
    "Question": "a giant Inhuman bulldog whose super abilities include teleportation",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "67",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Inhumans",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Inhumans",
    "Question": "a group of Marvel superheroes whose stories focus on the royal family",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "69",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Inhumans",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Venom",
    "Question": "a sentient alien symbiote with an amorphous form needs to bond with a host to survive ",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "86",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Amazing Spider-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "SHIELD",
    "Question": "a special law enforcement and counter-terrorism agency in the MCU",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "65",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Punisher",
    "Question": "A vigilante who wears a skull like logo on his body armor",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "57",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "The Punisher",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Beast",
    "Question": "A X-Men mutant possessing animal-like strength and agility",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "58",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Warlock",
    "Question": "Adam ________,  a synthetic being created by human scientists named \"The Enclave\"",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "81",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Silver Surfer",
    "Question": "an alien with metallic skin who travels through space riding a surfboard",
    "Answer Letters": "13",
    "Question Letters": "72",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Silver Surfer",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Vision",
    "Question": "an android built by Ultron to be the \"perfect being\" who helps defeat Ultron",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "76",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Scott Lang",
    "Question": "Ant-Man's secret identity",
    "Answer Letters": "10",
    "Question Letters": "25",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Ant-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Drax",
    "Question": "Arthur Douglas we recreated as ______ to destroy Thanos",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "55",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Mansion",
    "Question": "Avenger's _____ is where these superheroes live",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "47",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Rocket",
    "Question": "bio-engineered animal who is part of the Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "64",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Bolt",
    "Question": "Black _____, king of the Inhumans, who must remain silent",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "57",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Inhumans",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hulk",
    "Question": "Bruce Banner is _____",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "21",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Hulk",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Winter Soldier",
    "Question": "Bucky Barnes is _______",
    "Answer Letters": "14",
    "Question Letters": "23",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "America",
    "Question": "Captain ______",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "14",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Britain",
    "Question": "Captain ______, ",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "16",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Marvel",
    "Question": "Captain ______, the most powerful female super hero",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "51",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain Marvel",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Steve Rogers",
    "Question": "Captain America's secret identity",
    "Answer Letters": "12",
    "Question Letters": "33",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Danvers",
    "Question": "Carol ______, Captain Marvel's secret identity",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "46",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain Marvel",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Marvel",
    "Question": "Carol Danvers is also known as Captain ________",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "47",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain Marvel",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hawkeye",
    "Question": "Clint Barton is _____",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "21",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Drax",
    "Question": "Created by Mentor & Kronos to destroy Thanos",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "44",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Strange",
    "Question": "Doctor _____",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "12",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Strange",
    "Question": "Doctor Strange first appeared in ______ Tales",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "45",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Sanctorum",
    "Question": "Doctor Strange's home is called Sanctum _______",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "47",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Beast",
    "Question": "Dr. Hank McCoy is also the ________",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "35",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Doctor Strange",
    "Question": "Dr. Stephen _______",
    "Answer Letters": "14",
    "Question Letters": "19",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Agamotto",
    "Question": "Dr. Strange wears the Eye of _____ around his neck",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "50",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Frost",
    "Question": "Emma _____, once a villain, later joins the X-Men",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "49",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Luke Cage",
    "Question": "Failed prison experiment gave him unbreakable skin & superhuman strength",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "72",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Luke Cage",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Helicarrier",
    "Question": "flying aircraft carrier, S.H.I.E.L.D.mobile command center",
    "Answer Letters": "11",
    "Question Letters": "58",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Howard Stark",
    "Question": "Founder of Stark Industries",
    "Answer Letters": "12",
    "Question Letters": "27",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Iron-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Castle",
    "Question": "Frank _______, the Punisher",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "27",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "The Punisher",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Punisher",
    "Question": "Frank Castle is the __________",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "30",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Rocket",
    "Question": "Groot's best friend",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "19",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Iron-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hogan",
    "Question": "Happy _____ is Tony Starks driver, body guard, and assistant",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "60",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Suspense",
    "Question": "Hawkeye made his first appearance in Tales of ______",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "52",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Thor",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Heimdall",
    "Question": "he guards the Bifrost Bridge",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "28",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Thor",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Drax",
    "Question": "His family was killed by Thanos, he now lives to get revenge",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "60",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Wakanda",
    "Question": "Home of the Black Panther",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "25",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Black Panther",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Duckworld",
    "Question": "Howard the Duck comes from the planet",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "37",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Howard the Duck",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Cigars",
    "Question": "Howard the Duck smokes _______",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "30",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Howard the Duck",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Tony Stark",
    "Question": "Iron-Man's secret identity",
    "Answer Letters": "10",
    "Question Letters": "26",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Iron-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "War Machine",
    "Question": "James Rhodes is ________",
    "Answer Letters": "11",
    "Question Letters": "24",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Grey",
    "Question": "Jean ____, member of the X-Men",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "30",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ghost Rider",
    "Question": "Johnny Blaze is _______",
    "Answer Letters": "11",
    "Question Letters": "23",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Ghost Rider",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Shawowcat",
    "Question": "Kitty Pryde is also _________, and a member of the X-Men",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "56",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Captain America",
    "Question": "Known for his shield",
    "Answer Letters": "15",
    "Question Letters": "20",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Cage",
    "Question": "Luke ____, married Jessica Jones",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "32",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Luke Cage",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Watson",
    "Question": "Mary Jane _____, married Peter Parker/Spider-Man",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "48",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Amazing Spider-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hawkeye",
    "Question": "Master archer, member of the Avengers",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "37",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Shang-Chi",
    "Question": "master of the Ten Rings",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "23",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Shang-Chi",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Vibranium",
    "Question": "metal prized for its virtually indestructable nature, only found in Wakanda",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "75",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Fantastic",
    "Question": "Mr. _______, can stretch his body like rubber",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "45",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Fantastic Four",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Wasp",
    "Question": "Nadia Pym is ______",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "19",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Ant-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Romanova",
    "Question": "Natasha __________, also known as the Black Widow",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "49",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Black Widow",
    "Question": "Natasha Romanoff is _____",
    "Answer Letters": "11",
    "Question Letters": "25",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Dormannu",
    "Question": "Nemesis of Dr. Strange from the Dark Dimension",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "46",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Fury",
    "Question": "Nick _____, Director of SHIELD",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "30",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Groot",
    "Question": "Only says \"I am _____\"",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "22",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Carter",
    "Question": "Peggy _____, love interest of Captain America",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "45",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Star-Lord",
    "Question": "Peter Quill is _______",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "22",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Coulson",
    "Question": "Phil _____, SHIELD agent",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "24",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Wong",
    "Question": "Protects the New York Sanctum with Doctor Strange",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "49",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Richards",
    "Question": "Reed ________, leader of the Fantastic Four",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "43",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Fantastic Four",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Jones",
    "Question": "Rick _____, Hulk's closest confidant",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "36",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Hulk",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Raccoon",
    "Question": "Rocket is a bio-engineered ______",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "33",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Halfworld",
    "Question": "Rocket Raccoon comes from Planet ______",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "39",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Falcon",
    "Question": "Sam Wilson is the ________",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "26",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ant Man",
    "Question": "Scott Lang",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "10",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Ant-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Groot",
    "Question": "Sentient alien tree that keeps the universe safe",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "48",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Yondo",
    "Question": "Star Lord's \"adopted\" father",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "28",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ego",
    "Question": "Star Lord's father",
    "Answer Letters": "3",
    "Question Letters": "18",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Captain America",
    "Question": "Steve Rogers is ______",
    "Answer Letters": "15",
    "Question Letters": "22",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Thing",
    "Question": "Stony giant who is one of the Fantastic Four",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "44",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Fantastic Four",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Black Panther",
    "Question": "T'Challa is ________",
    "Answer Letters": "13",
    "Question Letters": "20",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Black Panther",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ancient",
    "Question": "The ______ One, is Soccer Supreme & Dr. Strange's mentor",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "56",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Avengers",
    "Question": "The _______ is a team of Marvel superheroes",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "43",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Avengers",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "X-Men",
    "Question": "The Beast first appeared in ",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "28",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Levitation",
    "Question": "The Cloak of ______ is worn by Dr. Strange",
    "Answer Letters": "10",
    "Question Letters": "42",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Dr. Strange",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Valkyrie",
    "Question": "The goddess Brunnhilde, one of Asgard's mightiest warriors",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "58",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Thor",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Asgard",
    "Question": "The home of Thor, Odin and the Valkyrie",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "39",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Thor",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Jarvis",
    "Question": "The loyal butler to the Stark family",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "36",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Iron-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Sam Wilson",
    "Question": "The secret identity of the 2nd Captain America",
    "Answer Letters": "10",
    "Question Letters": "46",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Captain America",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Danger",
    "Question": "The X-Men train in the specially built_______ Room",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "50",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Loki",
    "Question": "Thor's adopted brother",
    "Answer Letters": "4",
    "Question Letters": "22",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Thor",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Iron Man",
    "Question": "Tony Stark is ______",
    "Answer Letters": "8",
    "Question Letters": "20",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Iron-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Klaue",
    "Question": "Ulysses _____, in Black Panther",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "31",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Black Panther",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Angel",
    "Question": "Warren Kenneth Worthington III is an X-man, also known as",
    "Answer Letters": "5",
    "Question Letters": "57",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "X-Men",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Thanos",
    "Question": "Wiped out half the population of the universe",
    "Answer Letters": "6",
    "Question Letters": "45",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Star-Lord",
    "Question": "Yondo's \"adopted\" son",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "21",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "Guardians of the Galaxy",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Spiderman",
    "Question": "Your friendly neighborhood _______",
    "Answer Letters": "9",
    "Question Letters": "34",
    "Category": "Super Heros",
    "Publisher": "Marvel",
    "Series": "The Amazing Spider-Man",
    "Universe": "MCU",
    "Difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Absorbing",
    "Question": "______ Man, can take on the properties of any material he touches",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Barracuda",
    "Question": "A ruthless criminal and assissin who hunted the Punisher",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Cannonball",
    "Question": "Human ______, is supervillian appearing in Marvel comics",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Chameleon",
    "Question": "Spider-man's first adversay in The Amazing Spider-Man #1",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Deathstrike",
    "Question": "Laky _______, ",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Dormammu",
    "Question": "one of Doctor Strange's fiercest advesaries",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Galactus",
    "Question": "a cosmic entity that consumes planets to sustain its life force",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Green Goblin",
    "Question": "Norman Osborn turns into the",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Green Goblin",
    "Question": "a Halloween-themed supervillain that flies on a hoverboard",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Juggernaut",
    "Question": "a villian whose head is like a battering ram",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Kingpin",
    "Question": "a crime overlord, advesary of Spider-Man,Daredevil, Hawkeye, andthe Punisher",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Kraven",
    "Question": "_______, the Hunter, one of Spider-Man's advesaries",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Maximus",
    "Question": "both a member of and antagonist to the Inhumans",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Morbius",
    "Question": "A vampire inspired Spider-Man advesary, he became an antihero with his own series",
    "Answer Letters": "7",
    "Question Letters": "81",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Mastermind",
    "Question": "Jason Wyngrade, is also the supervillian _______",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Molten Man",
    "Question": "One of Spider-Man's early advesaries, his body can generate extreme heat and radiation",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Norman",
    "Question": "____ Osborn, global industrialist and the Green Goblin",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Octopus",
    "Question": "Doctor _____, Spider-man's first villian",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Omega",
    "Question": "_______ Red, ",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Puppet",
    "Question": "______ Master, first appeared in Fantastic Four #8",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Rhino",
    "Question": "A green colored villian with a horn on his head, early Spider-Man advesary",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ronan",
    "Question": "______ the Accuser, is the Supreme Accuser of the Kree Empire and works with Thanos",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Sinister",
    "Question": "Mr. ______, ",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Sentinels",
    "Question": "mutant-hunting robots, usually advesaries of the X-Men.",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Collector",
    "Question": "created a massive museum of life forms and artifacts from across the MCU",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Ultron",
    "Question": "a self-aware, highly intelligent robot who develops a god complex and a grudge against his creator Hank Pym",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Vulture",
    "Question": "Adrian Toomes is the flying supervillian called the _______",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Struker",
    "Question": "Baron von _______ is an eneny of SHIELD and the Avengers",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Sinister",
    "Question": "the _______ Six, a group of villians organized by Doctor Octopus",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Sinister Six",
    "Question": "a group originallly composed of Doc Oc, Vulture, Electro, Mysterio, Sandman & Kraven",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Enforcers",
    "Question": "Team of villians originally consisting of Montana, the Ox, and Fancy Dan",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Cerebro",
    "Question": "Device created by Professor X to detect humans and mutants",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Skrulls",
    "Question": "a race of extraterrestial shapeshifters who appear in many Marvel comic series",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Destroyer",
    "Question": "an animated suit of Asguardian armor that plagues Thor",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Hydra",
    "Question": "Baron von Strucker's terrorist organization prominent in the MCU",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  },
  {
    "Answer": "Thanos",
    "Question": "a powerful villian in the MCU, he has a twisted moral compass and thinks his actions are justified.",
    "Answer Letters": "",
    "Question Letters": "",
    "Category": "",
    "Publisher": "",
    "Series": "",
    "Universe": "",
    "Difficulty": ""
  }
]